industrybuying.com 2017-12-01

# Privacy Policy - Industrybuying.com

## Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting IndustryBuying.com. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be usedi. 

**Note:** _  the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for IndustryBuying.com only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites._

### Collection of Information

We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill you specific request. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists. 

### Cookie/Tracking Technology

The Site uses cookies and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookies and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties. 

### Distribution of Information

We may disclose to third party services certain personally identifiable information listed below: 

  * Information you provide us such as name, email, mobile phone number 
  * Information we collect as you access and use our service, including device information, location and network carrier 

This information is shared with third party service providers so that we can: 

  * Personalize the app for you 
  * Perform behavioral Analytics 

### Commitment to Data Security

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. 

### Online Advertising We Use

We use Google Analytics Advertising Features for remarketing to advertise across the Internet. Remarketing will display relevant ads tailored to you based on what parts of the IndustryBuying.com website you have viewed by placing a cookie on your machine. THIS COOKIE DOES NOT IN ANYWAY IDENTIFY YOU OR GIVE ACCESS TO YOUR COMPUTER. The cookie is used to say "This person visited this page, so show them ads relating to that page." Google Analytics remarketing allows us to tailor our marketing to better suit your needs and only display ads that are relevant to you. 

If you do not wish to participate in our remarketing, you can opt out by using the [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/). 

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
